Hello friends welcome back to Domination Price
Action and Volume Action please
welcome to the live session see today
ICICI Lombard is
trading here and they are also
trading on the short side here in the morning
itself this stock here has been shared with you
on the Telegram channel ok
ICICI
its meaning is that the price can come to this supply
zone and reverse again ok
so now look at the price right now look at the price here the
price is here in the same supply zone ok so
we have shorted ICICI Lombard
and how to make a short entry in it
we are going to discuss in today's session so
let's first go to the
daily chart here let's
understand simply
look at this
ICICI Lombard's price
action here ok what is it here the price is moving
downwards ok and after that
look at this candle look at the
rate candle here look inside this rate candle
ok what has happened in sessions one, two and three the
price is this  The price is inside the rate candle.
Okay, what happened in the previous session,
what did the price do? It
tried to break the high of this candle here. It tried to go up,
but see how the price came down again. Okay,
and how it came down, the
price came down with high volume. So, for this reason,
what have we done, we have selected ICICI Lombard for the
short side here for today.
See, from the basic channel,
stock selection piece, six advance
energy also happens. Okay, so see here,
how to enter, we are going to discuss here now. So
let's go to another
time frame here.
Now,
understand the morning activity here.
Okay, now here in this dress,
we have the setup of Domination Price Action Method
here on the short side.
Okay, now see what we did here, as soon as the
low of this candle is visible, the scam has broken here.
What have we done, see, we had to wait the
price. Actually, this line is
visible to you here. We had to wait the price till here.  We had to let it
come till here,
okay, but this registration has been done, okay, we have
entered here, our stop loss was
above here, so we had to let the
price come till here, now
see the price, we had to enter till there,
but because this registration was coming from here,
we entered here, okay, a
little entry has been done here,
we have shorted here, sorry,
from here, okay,
let's see here, friends,
see the price action of ICICI Lombard here, the
price action was exactly here,
side by side, okay,
we had shorted from the black line visible here,
but actually we had to short from here,
which we have discussed here earlier,
okay, now see the price had
come down from here, okay, so
look here, the price has come down by about 1:1.5,
and again, by
going to the same line, the side
action is visible here, so
see, what we have done here is that we have
squared off the position here,
okay, the
current price is within the first candle, okay, the
reason for this is  This side of the truth is also within the
first five minute candle of this market,
rate the price here right now, okay, so
what was the importance of this line here
and what is the price doing here right now,
above the same line,
trade here and it is also possible that the
price may move upwards from here
because what is the price doing here,
above the same line or the CD
activity is showing here, so
what have we done to the position, we have squared
up, okay
and see from here, the price is
going upwards from here right now, okay, so dear
friend, if you liked this video, then
please like this video and if
you have not yet subscribed to our channel, then
subscribe to the channel
and those members who want to learn domination price in
volume action, want to learn some
quality,
want to learn the setup of professional trade, those members please
join the Telegram channel,
all the details are given there, you will get it
in the next video, thank you